{
    "subject": "resource/Anti-Scrunti_Faction",
    "predicate": "ontology/bandMember",
    "object": "resource/Leslie_Mah",
    "human_readable": "Leslie Mah is a band member of Anti-Scrunti Faction.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.946768581867218,
            "question": "Does Leslie Mah play in any other bands besides Anti-Scrunti Faction?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9263190031051636,
            "question": "What band is Leslie Mah a member of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8849586248397827,
            "question": "Name a band that Leslie Mah belongs to."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7964861989021301,
            "question": "Is Leslie Mah a musician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7947344183921814,
            "question": "Who is Leslie Mah?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7151306867599487,
            "question": "What is Anti-Scrunti Faction known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6872411370277405,
            "question": "What is the name of the band that Leslie Mah plays in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6699215173721313,
            "question": "What genre of music does Anti-Scrunti Faction play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6614489555358887,
            "question": "Where is Anti-Scrunti Faction from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5857314467430115,
            "question": "Are there any famous songs by Anti-Scrunti Faction?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Leslie Mah is a band member of Anti-Scrunti Faction.",
            "html": "dbpedia_808_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is Anti-Scrunti Faction from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_808_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre of music does Anti-Scrunti Faction play?",
            "html": "dbpedia_808_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the band that Leslie Mah plays in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_808_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_808_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_808_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_808_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_808_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_808_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_808_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_808_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_808_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_808_95.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_808_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. According to file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_808/re-ranker-msmarco/23.txt, Leslie Mah and Lynn Breedlove were consistent members of Tribe 8, and according to file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_808/re-ranker-msmarco/98.txt, Leslie Mah was a member of Anti-Scrunti Faction before joining Tribe 8."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that confirms Leslie Mah was indeed a member of the band Anti-Scrunti Faction, playing bass and singing."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}